<?xml version="1.0"?>
<member id="vasilakisn" group="g_istlab g_iris" joined="20130101">
	<givenname>Nikos</givenname>
	<surname>Vasilakis</surname>
	<memb_title>Mr.</memb_title>
	<email>nvasilakis@aueb.gr</email>
	<!-- <web_site></web_site> -->
	<office_phone>+30 2108203687</office_phone>
	<!-- <mobile_phone></mobile_phone> -->
	<!-- <fax></fax> -->
	<!-- <alumnus/>--><!-- Optional -->
	<office_address>
		Office 907, 47A Evelpidon & 33 Lefkados str, 113 62 Athens, Greece
	</office_address>
	<postal_address>
		76 Patission str, 104 34 Athens, Greece
	</postal_address>
	<photo>../images/nvasilakis.jpg</photo>
	<shortcv>
			<p><i>Nikolaos-Dimitrios (Nikos) Vasilakis</i> is a PhD candidate/ researcher at the Athens University of Economics and Business (AUEB) in the Management of Information Systems in the healthcare (ELTRUN/ ISTLab). He holds a BSc (Hons) in Management Science and Technology (AUEB, Greece, 2008), and an MPhil in Innovation, Strategy and Organization (Judge Business School - University of Cambridge, UK, 2011). For his studies, he has been honored with scholarships by the Lilian Voudouri Foundation (2011) and George and Victoria Karelia Foundation (2013, 2014, 2015).
			He has worked in research projects on the use and role of information systems in health reform, RFID applications in hospitals, e-government, and shared logistics practices in an urban environment. He has also worked as a Business Intelligence Consultant at Relational Technology SA (2008-2010) and as a Blue Book Trainee at the European Commission (2014). He is co-founder of Healthier, a mobile personal health management assistant.
			His research interests lie in the adoption and implementation of Information Systems, the dynamics and interactions within (formalized and informally emerging) networks, and the relevant role of particular individuals as change agents.</p>
	</shortcv>
	<phd-info completed="0" supervisor="m_pouloudi" startdate="20130101">
    <phd-title>Management of Information Systems in the Healthcare</phd-title>
    <phd-summary></phd-summary>
  </phd-info>
</member>